Brandon Mazikowski

Software Engineer

San Jose, CA

408-857-1993 <u>email me</u> <u>linkedin</u> <u>portfolio</u>

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with 12+ years experience in customer service. Natural ability to promote products and build rapport through listening and communication skills. Well rounded individual in oral communication and experience with working in groups. Energetic self-starter with strong communication skills; work well independently or on a team. Ambitious, flexible team member who loves to learn. Skilled problem-solver and multi-tasker.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Node, MongoDB/Mongoose, Express, SQL, Ruby, and Ruby on Rails. Created full-stack web applications, using recursive algorithms and web forms. Leveraged debugging strategies to ensure program integrity. Plan, wrote, tested, deployed and launched a full-stack application. Leveraged third-party APIs and integrated them into websites and applications. Developed a portfolio of individual and collaboratively built projects

PROJECTS

Storefront app - Mongoose, Express, Node, jQuery and Bootstrap.

The next Yelp app - MERN stack with one other developer.

First todo - Ruby and React with 3 other developers

Wallpaper - React Native.

WaterCooler - MERN stack with 3 other developers and a UX/UI team.

EXPERIENCE

Deputy Sheriff: Santa Clara County Sheriff - Santa Clara, CA February 2019 - June 2020

- We worked as a group to make things happen, but completed tasks on our own when a partner was not around.
- I considered my colleagues to be family and I worked well with every one of them.

Fitness Coach: Mint condition Fitness - Los Gatos, CA

February 2017-2018

- The position I was in required a great deal of multitasking, being able to correct 3 different members at once, while being able to carry on 3 different conversations.
- I worked in a team environment with 6 other trainers and we all shared clients.

Brandon's Cross Fitness Training: Los Gatos/Gilroy, CA

February 2007-2016

- Working and talking with people is what makes my job enjoyable and worthwhile.
- This company has given me many challenges through the years, and I enjoyed stepping up and pushing myself in each and every one.

EDUCATION

General Assembly - Online 2020 to 2021

Software Engineer

Gavilan College-Gilroy, CA 2012 to 2016

Graduated with AA in kinesiology sports medicine

West Valley College -Saratoga, CA 2001-2004

Graduated with AA in communications/Liberal arts